This is your Chave?
Yeah.
65 to frame off restoration. And how proud is it?
Did a lot of work to it. How you've been working on it.
Four years. I purchased the system bill
and um, we did everything that I have to do,
motor, trams, everything.
Wow. Ooh, that's beautiful. Yeah, you want to hear it?
So I was here, Gary, he's the painter.
He's the one doing all the paperwork on
his thing. Oh, okay. Hey Ivan.
Good to meet you man. How you doing?
So what is this beauty gonna be done?
It? This spray. Oh, this spray. Yeah.
You just gotta be really particular with it, you know,
it's all a process of, of time
and, you know, a lot of, a lot of work, a lot of things
that gotta happen before we get it all to get in a spray.
So everybody talks about how great you guys are.
I can't imagine what your
own personal car's gonna look like.
Oh, this one's got his signature all over it. So
What is his Signature? It knows
this. It's gonna be flawless.
This will be the cream of the crop for I,
you won't find a better restoration than
what we've done four years in the making.
So I, I gotta come back in the spring
so I can see. Oh, you
Will? Yeah. Yeah.